{
    "id": "dc2207a5dd3a4e7c865c9f77be99f401",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The boy ……………………. the girl is guilty.",
            "description": "The verb is singular when you connect two singular nouns with as well as. Or you can write 'The boy and the girl are guilty.'",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1ef4e823fdf740dbbe4f0a991b537b31"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… being rich, he does not help anyone.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition it is followed by a noun or ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Despite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b786ff237104bd3b4924b14a593c435"
        },
        {
            "question": "He tried hard ……………………, he could not succeed.",
            "description": "However is not a conjunction use a semicolon or a full stop before however. ",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "however",
                "even as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a247397a07f54cfc8c2f4e4f744c204a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He won’t marry ………………………. he gets a good job.",
            "description": "Until shows time.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "up to",
                "as long as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "07b206545ef14913ab75541aee2bd2a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must work hard ……………………. you will fail.",
            "description": "Or presents an alternative.",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "or",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "536e7bba20634cdcb7c76bdfdeda548f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ought to be here soon …………………….. she left office at",
            "description": "For can mean because in a more formal style. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fa46eb3a862f4e7a96a18ff6c11dcb81"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. she is intelligent she is lazy.",
            "description": "Though is a conjunction used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Despite",
                "Even as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "21c9d10e881a4379863cd2025d8654d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… he was not feeling well, they took him to hospital.",
            "description": "As gives the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Hence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24856ab3581d4ac891c69a19215ea191"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tomorrow is a holiday, ……………………. he will be at home.",
            "description": "So gives the result.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5fb3cb4aa2874dc1b290b5a7d562d6d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I last visited my parents five months …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "ago",
                "past"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6266fa58c4e34b29ae06189969ee056f"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the school ……………………. he studied.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which. ",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "there",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "19189d0a5bba4e9689b07117467c9481"
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been months …………………….. it rained.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "from",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "603d1c54393e4da88ba74c1c4d513904"
        }
    ]
}